Melvin N. Gough Papers, 1919-1971
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
- Reliability—clippings and reports, 1953-1954. (Box-folder 10-22)
- Take-off—performance indicators, 1953-1954. (Box-folder 10-23)
- De Haviland Comet, c.1953-1955. (Box-folder 10-24)
- Names and addresses, c.1953-1955. (Box-folder 10-25)
- Crash fires, c.1953-1956. (Box-folder 10-26)
- Ditching, 1953-1956. (Box-folder 10-27)
- Speeches, c.1953-1957. (Box-folder 10-28)
- Telephone calls, 1953-1957. (Box-folder 11-1)
- Air Safety Digest, 1953-1958. (Box-folder 11-2)
- Cockpit layout standardization, 1953-1958. (Box-folder 11-3)
- Jets—piloting problems, 1953-1958. (Box-folder 11-4)
- Navion, L-17A, Bonanza Airplanes, 1953-1958. (Box-folder 11-5)
- Security, 1953-1958. (Box-folder 11-6)
- AGARD (Paris)—notebook, 1954. (Box-folder 11-7)
- Air France Super Constellation accident, Idlewild Airport, N.Y., 1954. (Box-folder 11-8)
- AGARD Flight Test Manual, Chapter III Draft (Johnson), 1954. (Box-folder 11-9)
- Daily log, 1954. (Box-folder 11-10)
- Dutch K.L.M. 1049 Lockheed Super-Constellation accident, Shannon, Ireland, 1954. (Box-folder 11-11)
- Emergency access devices on pilot enclosures, 1954. (Box-folder 11-12)
- Emergency procedures, 1954. (Box-folder 11-13)
- Felker Heliport, Fort Eustis, 1954. (Box-folder 11-14)
- "Flight Tests of Airplanes Equipped with Irreversible Servo Controls" (Lefebvre), 1954. (Box-folder 11-15)
- Flight Safety Foundation Conference, 1954. (Box-folder 11-16)
- "High-Speed Stability and Control Problems" (Phillips), 1954. (Box-folder 11-17)
- Martin Company—visit, 1954. (Box-folder 11-18)
- NACA reports, 1954. (Box-folder 11-19)
- Pilot error—clippings, 1954. (Box-folder 11-20)
- "Some Applications of Experiments and Theoretical Analysis in Accident Investigations" (Rhode), 1954. (Box-folder 11-21)
- Supersonic fighters, 1954. (Box-folder 11-22)
- Thrust—talk presented at operational conference, Cleveland, Ohio, November 17-18, 1954. (Box-folder 11-23)
- Thrust-reversal in turbo-propelled aircraft, 1954. (Box-folder 11-24)
- "Turbine Transports," 1954. (Box-folder 11-25)
- Helicopter research projects, 1954-1955. (Box-folder 12-1)
- "Jet Instrumentation Problems," "Toward Better Instrumentation" (Gough), 1954-1955. (Box-folder 12-2)
- Jet thrust reversals, 1954-1955. (Box-folder 12-3)
- AGARD, 1954-1957. (Box-folder 12-4)
- Air Research and Development Command Flying Safety Newsletters, 1954-1957. (Box-folder 12-5)
- Aviation Medicine Residency Program, 1954-1958. (Box-folder 12-6)
- Tires, 1954-1958. (Box-folder 12-7)
- Jet takeoff safety—reports, correspondence, 1954-1961. (Box-folder 12-8)
- Boeing 707, c.1854-1961. (Box-folder 12-9)
- Passenger flying—articles, 1954-1963. (Box-folder 12-10)
- Angle-of-attack, c.1954-1965. (Box-folder 12-11)
- Aero Commander 680F—handling qualities, c.1955. (Box-folder 12-12)
- Airframe and engine icing problems, 1955. (Box-folder 12-13)
- "Automatic Control of Gust Response" (Kraft), 1955. (Box-folder 12-14)
- Boundary layer control, 1955. (Box-folder 12-15)
- Buck, Robert N.—articles, 1955. (Box-folder 12-16)
- Coanda effect, 1955. (Box-folder 12-17)
- Daily log, 1955. (Box-folder 12-18)
- Institute of the Aeronautical Sciences fellowships, 1955. (Box-folder 12-19)
- NACA reports, 1955. (Box-folder 12-20)
- "Reliability and Safety as Design Parameters" (Stieglitz), 1955. (Box-folder 12-21)
- "Report on the Shooting Down of El Al Aircraft 4x- AKC," 1955. (Box-folder 12-22)
- X-1B, X-1E, D-558-2 rocket research airplanes—photos, 1955. (Box-folder 12-23)
- F-101A, 1955. (Box-folder 12-24)
- Ingestion screens, 1955-1956. (Box-folder 12-25)
- JRF-5 accident, 1955-1956. (Box-folder 12-26)
- Turboprop engines—performance, 1955-1956. (Box-folder 12-27)
- Stall warning systems, 1955-1957. (Box-folder 12-28)
- Field of view—visibility, 1955-1958. (Box-folder 13-1)
- Vertical take-off aircraft, 1955-1963. (Box-folder 13-2)
- "Analysis of Lift-Curve Slopes Determined in Flight of a Flexible Swept-Wing Jet Bomber" (Aiken and Fisher), 1956. (Box-folder 13-3)
- "An Analysis of Vertical Tail Loads Measured in Flight on a Swept-Wing Bomber Airplane" (McGowan and Cooney), 1956. (Box-folder 13-4)
- Boeing XB-47D Stratojets—clippings, 1956. (Box-folder 13-5)
- B-29 D558-2 accident, 1956. (Box-folder 13-6)
- Comparison of F-100 wind tunnel and flight spin, c.1956. (Box-folder 13-7)
- Confederate Air Force, c.1956. (Box-folder 13-8)
- Daily log, 1956. (Box-folder 13-9)
- Eastern Airlines Martin 404 accident, Owensboro, KY, 1956. (Box-folder 13-10)
- "Flight Investigation of the Fuselage Deformations on a Swept-Wing Bomber During Push-Pull Maneuvers" (Mayo), 1956. (Box-folder 13-11)
- Flight Safety Foundation Award, 1956. (Box-folder 13-12)
- Hypoxia and undetermined jet accidents, 1956. (Box-folder 13-13)
- International Civil Aviation Organization Papers, 1956. (Box-folder 13-14)
- "A Modified Matrix Method..." (Gainer and Aiken), c.1956. (Box-folder 13-15)
- NACA reports, 1956. (Box-folder 13-16 to 13-18 (3 folders))
- National Aeronautical Laboratory (Japan)—visit, 1956. (Box-folder 13-19)
- Netherlands—maps, etc., 1956. (Box-folder 13-20)
- "Notes on Correlation of Model and Full-Scale Spin Recovery Characteristics" (Gough), 1956. (Box-folder 13-21)
- "Tire-Runway Braking Friction Coefficients" (Gough, Sawyer, Trant), 1956. (Box-folder 13-22)
- Thrustmeter—notes and photos, 1956. (Box-folder 13-23)
- XP6M-1 accident, 1956. (Box-folder 13-24)
- "Flight Measurements of Some of the Flying Qualities and Stability Derivatives of the Chance F8U-1 Airplane" (Kraft, McLaughlin, White), c.1956. (Box-folder 13-25)
- "AGARD's views about flight safety and pilot selection" [Bergeret]; pilot error—clippings, 1956-1957. (Box-folder 13-26)
- Flight Safety Foundation—bulletins, 1956-1957. (Box-folder 13-27)
- Reliability—clippings, 1956-1957. (Box-folder 13-28)
- Angle-of-attack, 1956-1958. (Box-folder 13-29)
- Approach and runway lights, 1956-1958. (Box-folder 13-30)
- Institute of the Aeronautical Sciences, 1956-1958. (Box-folder 14-1)
- AGARD—material From Dr. G. Bock, 1956-1958. (Box-folder 14-2)
- Skidding, 1956-1958. (Box-folder 14-3)
- Noise, c.1956-1959. (Box-folder 14-4)
- Angle-of-attack instrumentation, c.1956-1961. (Box-folder 14-5)
- Landing problems, c.1956-1965. (Box-folder 14-6)
- Helicopters—articles, 1956-1970. (Box-folder 14-7)
- AGARD—Flight Test Panel 7th General Assembly, 1957. (Box-folder 14-8)
- AGARD, 1957. (Box-folder 14-9)
- AGARD General Assembly—Washington, D.C., 1957. (Box-folder 14-10)
- AGARD—London—clippings, etc., 1957. (Box-folder 14-11)
- AGARD—London—preliminaries, 1957. (Box-folder 14-12)
- Atkins anti-collision light, 1957. (Box-folder 14-13)
- Av-Cir analysis and photographic report, 1957. (Box-folder 14-14)
- Communication—management, 1957. (Box-folder 14-15)
- Daily log, 1957. (Box-folder 14-16)
- Hiller X-18 tilt wing aircraft, Palo Alto, California, November 11-15, 1957. (Box-folder 14-17)
- "Flight and Analog Simulator Studies of an Automatically Controlled Interceptor" (Cheatham and Brissenden), c.1957. (Box-folder 14-18)
- H19B helicopter accident report, 1957. (Box-folder 14-19)
- "Effect of the Proximity of the First Wing Bending..." (Huss and Donegan), 1957. (Box-folder 14-20)
- NACA flight operations aircraft, 1957. (Box-folder 14-21)
- NACA reports, 1957. (Box-folder 15-1)
- Propjet ski transport, 1957. (Box-folder 15-2)
- SAE Committee S-7, 1957. (Box-folder 15-3)
- Takeoff progress indicator, 1957. (Box-folder 15-4)
- Tire wear, 1957. (Box-folder 15-5)
- "Understanding and Interpreting Pilot Opinon" (Cooper), 1957. (Box-folder 15-6)
- AGARD, 1957-1958. (Box-folder 15-7)
- F-8-U1, 1957-1958. (Box-folder 15-8)
- Northeast Airliner accident, Riker's Island, New York. 1957-1958. (Box-folder 15-9)
- TWA Lockheed 1049A accident, Grand Canyon (1956), 1957-1958. (Box-folder 15-10)
- Lists of files burned, 1957-1963. (Box-folder 15-11)
- "Accuracy at the Height of an ILS Glide Slope at the Outer Marker Beacon," 1958. (Box-folder 15-12)
- AGARD, 1958. (Box-folder 15-13 to 15-14 (2 folders))
- AGARD—flight test panel—questionaires, 1958. (Box-folder 15-15)
- AGARD—Paris, 1958. (Box-folder 15-16 to 15-18 (3 folders))
- AGARD—travel plans, 1958. (Box-folder 15-19)
- B47 cyclic load tests, 1958. (Box-folder 15-20)
- Boeing DC-3—notes, 1958. (Box-folder 15-21)
- "Control-Fixed Stability Derivatives" (Crane, McGlaughlin, and White), 1958. (Box-folder 15-22)
- "...Effects of Retreating Blade Stall...Helicopter Rotor Blade" (Ludi), 1958. (Box-folder 15-23)
- "External Interference Effects..." (Silsby), 1958. (Box-folder 15-24)
- F-11F-1—accident summary, July 1955-July 1957, 1958. (Box-folder 15-25)
- Helicopter airlift at Wallops island, 1958. (Box-folder 15-26)
- "IBM Code Heading for Recording Crash Injury and Survival Data from Accidents" (Hasbrook, et al), c.1958. (Box-folder 15-27)
- International Air Transport Association, 1958. (Box-folder 15-28)
- International Civil Aviation Organization, 1958. (Box-folder 15-29)
- "Landing and Taxiing Tests Over Various Types of Runway Lights" (Dreher and Batterson), 1958. (Box-folder 15-30)
- Minneapolis—Honeywell Regulator Co.—take-off monitor, 1958. (Box-folder 15-31)
- NACA reports, 1958. (Box-folder 15-32)
- New York Airways Sikorsky S-58 Accident, 1958. (Box-folder 15-33)
- "Philosophy of Airworthiness" (Tye); Reliability— Correspondence, 1958. (Box-folder 15-34)
- "Piloting Research Aircraft" (Walker), 1958. (Box-folder 15-35)
- "Requirements and Factors Which Influence Precision Landing Approaches," 1958. (Box-folder 15-36)
- SAE [Society of Automotive Engineers] committee S-9, 1958. (Box-folder 15-37)
- Society of Automotive Engineers—Denver, 1958. (Box-folder 15-38)
- Space exploration—articles, 1958. (Box-folder 16-1)
- Take-off monitor, 1958. (Box-folder 16-2)
- Gough, Melvin—vita, list of reports and speeches, 1958. (Box-folder 16-3)
- NASA—Organization, 1958-1959. (Box-folder 16-4)
- "Recommendations Regarding a National Civil Space Program" (NASA Special Committee on Space Technology), 1958-1959. (Box-folder 16-5)
- Reliability—clippings, 1958-1959. (Box-folder 16-6)
- Correspondence, A-B, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 16-7)
- Correspondence, C-D, 1958-1960. (Box-folder 16-8)
- Correspondence, E-F, 1958-1960. (Box-folder 16-9)
- Correspondence, G-H, 1958-1960. (Box-folder 16-10)
- Flight Safety Foundation, 1958-1960. (Box-folder 16-11)
- Instrumentation—Joseph Walker paper, letter, 1958-1960. (Box-folder 16-12)
- Telephone calls, 1958-1960. (Box-folder 16-13)
- Fires, 1958-1962. (Box-folder 16-14)
- Speeches, writings, miscellaneous articles, 1958-1963. (Box-folder 16-15)
- Alford, William—death, 1959. (Box-folder 16-16)
- American Rocket Society, 1959. (Box-folder 16-17)
- Barbour Award—notices, 1959. (Box-folder 16-18)
- Bomarc and Nike Hercules missiles/air defense, 1959. (Box-folder 16-19)
- Boundary layer control, 1959. (Box-folder 16-20)
- Daily log, 1959. (Box-folder 16-21)
- Events for, August 15-21, 1959. (Box-folder 16-22)
- Flight Safety Foundation—memo, bulletins, corresondence, 1959. (Box-folder 16-23)
- Flight Safety Foundation—notices and correspondence, 1959. (Box-folder 16-24)
- Glennan, T. Keith—address, Republic Research Center, June 18, 1959. (Box-folder 16-25)
- Jet Propulsion Lab—contractors meeting, August 21, 1959. (Box-folder 16-26)
- Johns Hopkins engineers—Joseph Truman Thompson Fund and Abel Wolman Fund, 1959. (Box-folder 16-27)
- Mercury Project—Congressional reports, 1959. (Box-folder 16-28)
- Official visit to AFMTC; fiscal year 1960— memorandums, August 15, 1959. (Box-folder 16-29)
- NASA—contract cuts, 1959. (Box-folder 16-30)
- NASA statement—research with British scientists, 1959. (Box-folder 16-31)
- "The Pilot's Role in Space Flight" (Westbrook), 1959. (Box-folder 16-32)
- "The Problem of Escape from Satellite Vehicles" (Carter and Huff), 1959. (Box-folder 16-33)
- Satellite payload—summary and correspondence, 1959. (Box-folder 16-34)
- SLV-6—progress report #3, 1959. (Box-folder 16-35)
- SLV-7—progress report, 1959. (Box-folder 16-36)
- "Spotlight on Safety" (Harris), 1959. (Box-folder 16-37)
- Thor (XSM-75) missile, c.1959. (Box-folder 16-38)
- Vanguard Thor-Able—memo and correspondence, 1959. (Box-folder 16-39)
- Atlantic missile range operations office, 1959-1960. (Box-folder 16-40)
- Flight safety—"Safety in the Jet Age" (Harris), 1959-1960. (Box-folder 16-41)
- Symposium—instruments, 1959-1960. (Box-folder 16-42)
- Travel, 1959-1960. (Box-folder 16-43)
- American Airlines accident—Laguardia, 1959-1961. (Box-folder 17-1)
- Fire, 1959-1963. (Box-folder 17-2)
- Miscellaneous NASA publications, 1959-1972. (Box-folder 17-3)
- "The Accident Investigator's View" (Tweedie), 1960. (Box-folder 17-4)
- AGARD—Paris, 1960. (Box-folder 17-5)
- Calendar, 1960. (Box-folder 17-6)
- Cleveland Hopkins Airport-crash and rescue operations—correspondence, 1960. (Box-folder 17-7)
- Crash safety of kerosene vs. aviation grade gasoline, 1960. (Box-folder 17-8)
- Helicopter accident—Chicago, 1960. (Box-folder 17-9)
- Northwest Airlines accident, 1960. (Box-folder 17-10)
- Miscellaneous correspondence, 1960. (Box-folder 17-11)
- "Reliability and Murphy's Law" (Burch); Office of Reliability and Systems Analysis, 1960. (Box-folder 17-12)
- "Satellite Instrumentation for Measurement of the Thermal Radiation Budget of the Earth" (Sucmi and Parent), c.1960. (Box-folder 17-13)
- U.S. Air Force safety congress, first annual, 1960. (Box-folder 17-14)
- Foreign accidents, 1960-1961. (Box-folder 17-15)
- Insurance, 1960-1961. (Box-folder 17-16)
- Lockheed Electra crashes, 1960-1961. (Box-folder 17-17)
- Lockheed Electra—meetings, 1960-1961. (Box-folder 17-18)
- Mid-air collision between TWA Constellation and United DC-8, Staten Island, NY, 1960-1961. (Box-folder 17-19 to 17-20 (2 folders))
- Sabena Airlines crash, 1960-1961. (Box-folder 18-1)
- SCAT (Speed Condition-Approach/Takeoff), 1960-1961. (Box-folder 18-2)
- Arctic-Pacific Inc., crash—Toledo, Ohio, 1960-1962. (Box-folder 18-3)
- Lockheed Electra crash—Boston, 1960-1962. (Box-folder 18-4 to 18-5 (2 folders))
- Reimbursement vouchers, 1960-1962. (Box-folder 18-6)
- UAL-TWA collision—New York, 1960-1962. (Box-folder 18-7)
- Notes and correspondence re: talks, 1960-1963. (Box-folder 18-8)
- DC-8, c.1960-1964. (Box-folder 18-9)
- Miscellaneous notes, 1960-1964. (Box-folder 18-10)
- Gough, Melvin—biographical information, 1960-1965. (Box-folder 18-11)
- Miscellaneous photographs, 1960-1969. (Box-folder 18-12)
- Miscellaneous publications, c.1960-1969. (Box-folder 18-13 to 18-14, 19-1 to 19-2 (4 folders))
- Altimeter—correspondence and articles, 1961. (Box-folder 19-3)
- American Airlines Electra accidents, 1959 and 1961, 1961. (Box-folder 19-4)
- Calendar, 1961. (Box-folder 19-5)
- Collisions, 1961. (Box-folder 19-6)
- Delta Airlines flight 744, Jacksonville, Florida, December 2, 1961. (Box-folder 19-7)
- "Fatal Airline Accident Investigations—Human Factors Team Approach" (Hopper), 1961. (Box-folder 19-8)
- Fiat G91 crash investigation, 1961. (Box-folder 19-9)
- Fiat G91 flight testing, 1961. (Box-folder 19-10)
- Lockheed Super-Constellation aircraft HK-177—Report of inquiries and transcription of hearings partial, 1961. (Box-folder 19-11)
- Miscellaneous correspondence, 1961. (Box-folder 19-12)
- "A Scientist Looks at Religion" (Dryden), 1961. (Box-folder 19-13)
- United Airlines DC-8 accident, Denver, July 11, 1961— correspondence, 1961. (Box-folder 19-14)
- VTOL-STOL—reports, 1961. (Box-folder 19-15)
- "Women in Space," 1961. (Box-folder 19-16)
- Boundary layer control, 1961-1962. (Box-folder 19-17)
- Civil Aeronautics Board—accident files, 1961-1962. (Box-folder 19-18 to 19-19 (2 folders))
- Correspondence and notes, 1961-1962. (Box-folder 20-1)
- Fire and fuel, 1961-1962. (Box-folder 20-2)
- Military accidents, 1961-1962. (Box-folder 20-3)
- Speeches, 1961-1962. (Box-folder 20-4)
- United Airlines DC-8 accident, Denver, Colorado, July 11, 1961—reports and photos, 1961-1962. (Box-folder 20-5)
- Variation and flutter, 1961-1962. (Box-folder 20-6)
- Fuels, 1961-1963. (Box-folder 20-7)
- Hazard properties of aviation fuels, 1961-1963. (Box-folder 20-8)
- Address to sixth IATA Public Relations Conference (Gough), 1962. (Box-folder 20-9)
- Altimeter research, 1962. (Box-folder 20-10)
- American Airlines Boeing 707 accident, Jamaica Bay, Long Island, 1962. (Box-folder 20-11 to 20-13 (3 folders))
- Angle-of-attack—correspondence, 1962. (Box-folder 20-14)
- Arresting gear, 1962. (Box-folder 20-15)
- Calendar, 1962. (Box-folder 20-16)
- Fire, 1962. (Box-folder 20-17)
- "Methodology and Patterns of Research in Aircraft Accidents" (Lederer), 1962. (Box-folder 20-18)
- Miscellaneous correspondence, 1962. (Box-folder 20-19)
- "Trends in Modern Aircraft Accident Investigation" (Gough), 1962. (Box-folder 20-20)
- Lightning, 1962. (Box-folder 20-21)
- Haldeman, George—correspondence, 1962-1964. (Box-folder 20-22)
- Personnel, c.1962-1969. (Box-folder 20-23)
- Tires and runways, 1962-1963. (Box-folder 20-24)
- Consultants—Soule, Sanders, 1962-1965. (Box-folder 20-25)
- Boundary layer control, 1963. (Box-folder 20-26)
- 15th Annual National Aerospace Electronics Conference, 1963. (Box-folder 20-27)
- Flying in turbulence, c.1963. (Box-folder 20-28)
- Flying qualities of modern light planes, 1963. (Box-folder 20-29)
- Institute of Science and Technology Navigation and Guidance Laboratory—meeting summary, 1963. (Box-folder 20-30)
- Manned spacecraft—reliability and quality control, 1963. (Box-folder 20-31)
- Speech by Addison M. Rothrock, at AIAA Space Flight Testing Conference, Cocoa Beach, Florida, March 18-20, 1963. (Box-folder 20-32)
- Vortac, 1963. (Box-folder 20-33)
- Vortex, 1963. (Box-folder 20-34)
- Severe turbulence operations testing—articles, reports, flight record data, 1963-1964. (Box-folder 20-35)
- Miscellaneous correspondence, 1963. (Box-folder 21-1)
- Mohawk Airlines Flight 112—accident, 1963. (Box-folder 21-2)
- NASA-DOD-FAA SST program coordination statement, 1963. (Box-folder 21-3)
- NWA airplane accident, Miami, Florida, February 2, 1963—correspondence, 1963. (Box-folder 21-4)
- Special Conference on General Aviation Safety, April 25, 1963. (Box-folder 21-5)
- Angle-of-attack, 1963-1965. (Box-folder 21-6)
- B-58 accidents, 1964. (Box-folder 21-7)
- Correspondence, notes—Mobile, Alabama, 1964. (Box-folder 21-8)
- F-105 problems and findings—transcript, 1964. (Box-folder 21-9)
- Kenyon Enterprises—Pilot Orientation Instrument, 1964. (Box-folder 21-10)
- Miscellaneous correspondence, 1964. (Box-folder 21-11)
- Paul Rosenberg—physics consultant, 1964. (Box-folder 21-12)
- Republic Aviation, 1964. (Box-folder 21-13 to 21-14 (2 folders))
- Specialties Inc., Chromosorter Web Scanner, 1964. (Box-folder 21-15)
- Specialties Inc., Flight tests of angle-of-attack transmitter casod [1961-1963], 1964. (Box-folder 21-16)
- Turbojet incidents and accidents, 1964. (Box-folder 21-17)
- Turbulence, 1964. (Box-folder 21-18)
- Severe turbulence operations testing—correspondence, 1964-1965. (Box-folder 21-19)
- X-15 research, 1964-1967. (Box-folder 21-20)
- Douglas C-133, 1965. (Box-folder 21-21)
- Flight Safety Foundation report, "Loss of Control of Swept-Wing Aircraft," 1965. (Box-folder 21-22)
- Miscellaneous correspondence, 1965. (Box-folder 21-23)
- Paradise Airlines Lockheed Constellation accident, Zephyr Cove, Nevada, 1965. (Box-folder 21-24)
- "Qualitative Stability and Control-Reevaluation of a C- 133A Aircraft" (Johnson and Benfield), 1965. (Box-folder 21-25)
- "Questions"—notebook, 1965. (Box-folder 21-26)
- "Survey of Ocurrences Involving Loss of Control of Swept-Wing Aircraft" (Project "Upset"), 1965. (Box-folder 22-1)
- Edwards—accidents, c.1965-1966. (Box-folder 22-2)
- C-133 airplane, 1965-1967. (Box-folder 22-3)
- NASA flight research center 258-3311-Extension 211 NAS 4-866, 1965-1967. (Box-folder 22-4)
- Miscellaneous correspondence, 1966. (Box-folder 22-5)
- NASA employment, 1966. (Box-folder 22-6)
- NASA Research Advisory Committee on Aircraft Operating Problems, 1966. (Box-folder 22-7)
- "Numerical Safety Goals" (Steiglitz), 1966. (Box-folder 22-8)
- Flight recorders, c.1966-1967. (Box-folder 22-9 to 22-11 (3 folders))
- Total inflight simulation, 1966-1971. (Box-folder 22-12)
- Apollo accident—clippings, articles, 1967. (Box-folder 22-13)
- Aviation Aircraft accidents—study, 1967. (Box-folder 22-14)
- DC-7, 1967. (Box-folder 22-15)
- Douglas C-133, 1967-1968. (Box-folder 22-16)
- Miscellaneous correspondence, 1967. (Box-folder 22-17)
- Pacific Airlines accident, Danville, California, May 7, 1964, 1967-1968. (Box-folder 22-18)
- Stack, John, 1967-1968. (Box-folder 22-19)
- Society of Experimental Test Pilots, 1967-1973. (Box-folder 22-20 to 22-21 (2 folders))
- Economic and Governmental Impact on Safety, 1968. (Box-folder 22-22)
- Litton Industries—consulting contract, 1968. (Box-folder 22-23)
- Manned space flight safety program, 1968. (Box-folder 22-24)
- Miscellaneous correspondence, 1968. (Box-folder 22-25)
- Balloon Platforms, AF—Cambridge Research Labs, 1969. (Box-folder 22-26)
- Miscellaneous correspondence, 1969. (Box-folder 22-27)
- Value Engineering Co. services, Alexandria, Virginia, 1969. (Box-folder 22-28)
- Other jobs, 1970. (Box-folder 22-29)
- Prospective team jobs for NASA, August 1970. (Box-folder 22-30)
- Concorde test flight, 1971. (Box-folder 22-31)
- George Haldeman—SST aircraft, 1971. (Box-folder 22-32)